sciencelearn.org.nz 2019-12-19

# Privacy — Science Learning Hub

  * Collection, storage and use of personal information
  * Collection and use of statistical information
  * Cookies
  * Privacy Commissioner

The purpose of this privacy policy is to let website users know when we collect personal information and what we do with it. We don’t use, share or transfer personal information in connection with the website except as set out in this policy or as otherwise set out somewhere on the website.

### Collection, storage and use of personal information

You can view materials on the website without disclosing any personal information.

However, you may choose to disclose personal information to us when you give feedback, in submission forms or if you choose to register with the website. This information will be viewable by site administrators, certain other members of the Science Learning Hub – Pokapū Akoranga Pūtaiao team and sometimes third-party contractors who administer or work on the website, provide us with services or work on special projects with us. Please don’t send us sensitive personal information or include any sensitive personal information in submission forms.

**Storage of information**

If you provide personal information, it will be held by the Science Learning Hub – Pokapū Akoranga Pūtaiao. It may be shared with third-party contractors to the extent necessary for them to administer or work on the website or to work on special projects with us. Email addresses are not made available to the public. Unless required by law, we will not publicise the names or email addresses of individuals who provide feedback to us without their consent.

**Use of personal information**

We will only use personal information provided to us for the purpose of administering, evaluating and improving the website, improving our services and communicating with you (including responding to your feedback and information provided in submission forms).

**Feedback**

Feedback is important to us, and we use it to evaluate and improve the website. If you provide feedback by email, through social media or via a third-party tool available through our website, that feedback will be sent to an appropriate Science Learning Hub – Pokapū Akoranga Pūtaiao team member. We may pass on relevant comments to other people who administer or contribute content to the website and to other stakeholders for the purposes of reporting. This could include your email address and other identifying information that you have provided.

**Registration**

Information submitted as part of the optional registration process will be accessible by website administrators and certain other members of the Science Learning Hub – Pokapū Akoranga Pūtaiao team. It may also be shared with other organisations for the purpose of reporting.

### Collection and use of statistical information

We may collect statistical information about your visit to the website to help us improve the website. This information is aggregated and does not identify you personally. It includes:

  * your IP address
  * the search terms you used
  * the pages you accessed on the website and the links and buttons you clicked on
  * the date and time you visited the website
  * the referring site (if any) you clicked through to this website
  * your operating system (e.g. Windows XP, Mac OS X)
  * the type of web browser you use (e.g. Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox)
  * where you scrolled to and where you clicked on pages within the website
  * information related to errors that occurred on the website while you were using it
  * other things such as your screen resolution and the language setting of your browser.

Some of this information is collected via third-party analytics and monitoring services. In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

**Use of statistical information**

The statistical information referred to above will be viewable by website administrators and certain other members of the Science Learning Hub – Pokapū Akoranga Pūtaiao team. It may also be shared with other organisations for the purpose of reporting.

### Cookies

This site generates cookies for the purpose of monitoring site usage and providing features such as logged-in sessions, favouriting of resources and so on. The cookies do not collect personal information. You can disable them or clear them from your web browser without affecting your ability to view website materials, although your ability to use functionality requiring a logged-in session (such as favouriting) will be impaired.

### Privacy Commissioner

If you are not satisfied with our response to any privacy-related concern, you can contact the Privacy Commissioner:

Office of the Privacy Commissioner  
PO Box 10-094  
Wellington, New Zealand  
Phone: (04) 474 7590  
Enquiries line (from Auckland): 302 8655  
Enquiries line (from outside Auckland): 0800 803 909  
Fax: (04) 474 7595  
Email: [enquiries@privacy.org.nz](mailto:enquiries@privacy.org.nz)
